Register of the Hugh Gibson papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- CORRESPONDENCE, 1902-1954 (Boxes 10-67)
  - Loudon, 1928-1929
  - Lubimoff, Ludmila, 1921-1933
  - Lubomirski, Casimir, Prince, 1920-1921
  - Lucas, Alice R., 1927
  - Luce, Clare Boothe, 1953-1954
  - Lucey, J. F., Capt., 1929
  - Lumley, Christopher, 1922
  - Lummis, Charles F., 1902-1911
  - Lunn, Henry, Sir, 1929
  - Luppe, Jean Bertrand de, Count, 1922
  - Lush, William G., 1923-1927
  - Lutz, Bertha(?), 1936
  - Lutz, Julian Herbert, 1931-1932
  - Lutz, Pinto, 1930
  - Lyell, Antony, 1938-1943
  - Lyman, Edward D., 1927
  - Lynch, Henry, Sir, 1936
  - Lyons, Maurice F., 1922
  - MacAndrews, John H. E., 1931 (Box 52)
  - Macatee, Robert B., 1919
  - Macauley, Adalin W. (Mrs. J. W.), 1927
  - McBride, Harry A., 1919-1921
  - McCabe, E. R., Col., 1921-1931
  - McCabe, Hilton H., 1954
  - MacCabes, 1922
  - McCarthy, Daniel J., 1927
  - McCarthy, E. Avery, 1928
  - McClure, Wallace, 1925
  - MacCochran, Clinton, 1924
  - McCook, Martha, 1920
  - McCormick, Anne O'Hare, 1952-1953
  - McCormick, Chauncey, 1919
  - McCormick, H., 1923
  - McCormick, Medill, 1921
  - McCormick, Mrs., 1938
  - McCoy, Frank, 1920-1923
  - MacCracken, Henry Noble, 1922-1924
  - McDermott, Michael James, 1932-1953
  - McDonald, D. C., Lt. Col., 1928-1933
  - MacDonald, Ramsay, 1929-1932
  - McFadden, George, 1919-1922
  - McKay, Arnold A., 1924
  - McKenna, J. G., 1920
  - MacKenzie, Cameron, 1921
  - MacKenzie, Dewitt, 1930
  - McLaughlin, William C., 1952
  - MacLeod, Louise, 1953
  - McLeod, Scott, 1954
  - MacLoghlin, James W., 1930
  - McManus, George Stuart, 1927-1928
  - MacMurray, John von Antwerp, 1930
  - MacNeil, Hugh, Mrs., 1931-1932
  - Macready, Gordon, 1922
  - McWilliams, Roy, 1929
  - Macy, Edward W., Maj., 1929
  - Madariaga, S., 1926-1930
  - Maglione, Luigi, 1924-1926
  - Magruder, Alexander R. [See also: SUBJECT FILE, Rogers Bill, Correspondence of Gibson], 1924
  - Magruder, Elinor P., 1924
  - Maguire, J. J., 1924
  - Maher, Thomas, Rev., 1931
  - Malcolm, Ian, Sir, 1922
  - Mallet, Victor A. L., 1931
  - Mallon, Dwight S., 1929
  - Mallone, Cecil L., Col., 1930
  - Malone, Dudley Field, 1930
  - Mangini, Armando, 1953
  - Marburg, Teodore, 1926
  - Marcosson, Isaac F., 1927-1929
  - Marden, C. S., 1920
  - Marks, Edward B., 1952-1954
  - Marriner, James Theodore
    - 1925-1927
    - 1928-1929
    - 1930-1933
  - Marshall, Hugh G., 1928-1933 (Box 53)
  - Marshall, William F., 1919-1921
  - Martin, Charles E., 1932
  - Martin, Charlotte D., 1952
  - Martin, Lawrence, 1920-1921
  - Martin, P. A., 1933
  - Martin, Walton, Mrs., 1952
  - Martin, William, 1925
  - Martin-Franklin, S., Count, 1933
  - Masaryk, Jan, 1929-1930
  - Mason, Alfred Bishop, 1931
  - Mason, Frank E., 1951-1954
  - Mason, Richard N., 1920-1933
  - Massigli, Rene, 1929-1932
  - Maton, 1928
  - Matthews, H. Freeman, 1953
  - Matthews, Julia Nelson (Mrs. Calvin Bruce), 1929
  - Maud, Harry, Col., 1919-1933
  - Maule, W. H. F., 1921-1930
  - Max Muller, William, Sir, 1922-1929
  - Maxse, H. F. B., 1923
  - Maxwell & Company, London [See: Hodson, Edward J.]
  - Mayer, 1922
  - Mayer, Ferdinand Lathrop [See also: DIPLOMATIC POSTS, Belgium, Correspondence with Embassy]
    - 1919-1931
    - 1932
    - 1933-1954
  - Mayhew, F. H., 1927-1930
  - Mayo, Katherine, 1925
  - Mayo, Margaret, 1933
  - Mayo, Paul, 1929
  - Mayr-Melendorff, Fritz, Baron, 1932
  - Mederos, Tomas S., 1928-1932
  - Medofsky, Martin, 1931
  - Medofsky, Morris, 1922-1927
  - Medofsky, Nathan, 1926-1933
  - Meeus, Adrien de, Count, 1928
  - Megevand, Mrs., undated
  - Mehta, Diwan Anantram, 1928
  - Melin, Anne, 1920
  - Melhorn, Kent C., 1932
  - Mendeville, Valdes, 1926
  - Merle-Smith, Van S., 1920
  - Merrill, Gregor C., 1930-1931
  - Merz, Charles, 1923
  - Mesmer, Joseph, 1929
  - Messersmith, George, 1927-1928
  - Mevius, Gustave de, Baron, 1929-1931
  - Meynard, Marie A., 1924-1927
  - Micara, Clemente, Cardinal, 1928-1952 (Box 54)
  - Michalski, St. (Nauka Polska, Warsaw), 1921
  - Michel, Mr., 1925
  - Middleton, Herbert P., 1924-1925
  - Mikolajczyk, Stanislaw, 1943
  - Milbank, Jeremiah, 1952
  - Miles, Basil and Daisy, (?)-1953, 1911
  - Military Order of the World War, Washington, D.C. (John Ross Delafield), 1930
  - Miller, Bernice [See also: Hoover, Herbert], 1952-1954
  - Miller, David Hunter, 1926
  - Miller, G. Harlan, 1925-1926
  - Miller, John C., 1921
  - Miller, Lily Murray, 1920
  - Miller, Ransford S., 1927
  - Miller, Raymond C., 1929-1933
  - Mimbela, 1926
  - Mitchell, Viola, 1929-1930
  - Mitchell, Wendell, 1932
  - Mlynarski, Emil, 1922-1927
  - Moffat, Curtis, 1930
  - Moffat, Jay Pierrepont
    - 1919-1920
    - 1921-1923
    - 1924-1938
  - Moncheur, Baron, 1924-1930
  - Money, M. J., 1927
  - Montefiore, Mrs., 1929
  - Montellano, Duc and Duchess de, 1927-1931
  - Montgomery, Monty (Mrs. Robert W.), 1953
  - Montille, L. de, 1919
  - Montini, J. B.(?), 1947-1954
  - Moore, Alexander P., undated
  - Moore, Ernest, 1932
  - Moore, Ernest C., 1929
  - Moore, J. Stanley, Maj., 1920
  - Moore, Thomas Ewing, 1928
  - Morand, Paul, 1908-1928
  - Morem(?), M., 1917
  - Morgan, Charles D., 1921
  - Morgan, Edwin, 1931-1933
  - Morgan, Gerald, 1922-1926
  - Morgan, Harry, undated
  - Morgan, Junius Spencer, 1931
  - Morgan, Harjes & Company, Paris, 1919
  - Morgenthau, Henry, 1919-1923
  - Morinni, Jacques de, Mrs., 1932
  - Morris, Alice V. (Mrs. Dave H.), 1925
  - Morris, David, 1933
  - Morrison, Thomas, 1922-1925
  - Morrow, Dwight W., 1927-1931
  - Morse, Clyly H., 1932
  - Morse, Frank W., 1920-1922
  - Moscicki, Michael C., 1952
  - Mosselman de Chenoy, Maj., 1928
  - Mott, T. Bentley, 1924-1925
  - Mowrer, Paul Scott, 1922
  - Muller, Max, 1926
  - Murdoch, W. L., Mrs., 1927
  - Murphy, Elmer, undated
  - Murphy, George H., 1924 June 13
  - Murphy, Ignatius I., 1930
  - Murphy, James J., 1924-1925
  - Murphy, Robert, 1953-1954
  - Murray, George D., 1931
  - Musaus, W. P., 1921-1925
  - Myers, Denys P., 1924-1929
  - Nabuco, Mauricio, 1952 (Box 55)
  - Nagai, M., 1928
  - Naliche, Count de, 1919
  - Nasmith, Charles Roy, 1921-1933
  - Nathan, Harry Lewis, 1930
  - National Committee For A Free Europe, Inc., N.Y., 1952
  - National Council For Prevention Of War, Washington, D.C. (Frederick J. Richy), 1929-1930
  - National Geographic Society, Washington, D.C., 1929
  - National Lutheran Council, N.Y., 1920
  - Neall, Adelaide, 1954
  - Needham, Harry, 1924
  - Neil, Margaret Verna, 1921-1922
  - Nerincx, Ida, 1927-1932
  - Neville, Edwin L., 1924
  - New Orient Society of Chicago (Henry Field), 1932
  - Newcome, W. A., 1921-1927
  - Newson, H. Dorsey [See also: SUBJECT FILE, Rogers Bill, Correspondence of Gibson], 1923-1935
  - Newton, Burkett Dunlap, 1927
  - Newton, Isaac B., 1927
  - Niblack, A. P., 1921
  - Nichols, William I. (This Week Magazine, N.Y.), 1952-1954
  - Nichols, William Wallace, 1926
  - Nickerson, Hoffman, 1953
  - Nixon, Agnes (Mrs. Robert H.), 1952
  - Noel-Baker, Philip, 1953-1954
  - Nolan, Dennis E., Gen., 1918-1929
  - Norrenberg, Marcel, 1927
  - Nortitz, Henriette, 1932
  - Norton, Edwin C., 1923-1924
  - Norton, Laurence H., 1924
  - Norweb, R. Henry, 1920-1933
  - Nowak, Jaroslav, 1921-1922
  - Nufia, Pedro, 1910
  - Nulton, L. M., 1927
  - Nulty, V. H., 1925
  - Nunez, Fernan, 1932
  - Nye, Joseph M., 1918-1932
  - O. E. McIntyre, Inc., N.Y., 1951
  - Oastler, Isabelle, 1932
  - Obermer, Nesta Seymour, 1922-1954
  - O'Connor, Hector, 1927-1929
  - Oechler, Henry V., 1952-1953
  - Office Francais de Protection des Refugies et Apatrides, Paris, 1954
  - Ogilvie, Paul M., 1920-1922
  - Ohlson, Ruth F., 1921
  - O'Laughlin, John Callan [See also: SUBJECT FILE, Rogers Bill, Correspondence of Gibson]
    - 1918-1920
    - 1921-1929
  - Olds, Robert E., 1926-1932
  - Olivaux, Ange, 1927
  - Olmsted, Florence Fay (Mrs. Remington), 1932
  - Olson, Reuel L., 1926
  - O'Melveny, H. W., 1922-1925
  - O'Neill, Meredith, 1921-1929
  - Orde, Captain, 1930
  - Ordynski, Richard, 1921
  - O'Reilly, Mary Boyle, 1921
  - Orr, Arthur, 1920-1932
  - The Osaka Mainichi Publishing Company, Ltd., Osaka & Tokyo, 1930
  - Osborne, Lithgow, 1918
  - Ostoja-Zagorska, Julius R. von, Mrs., 1933
  - Otto, Henry S., 1919
  - Oultremont, Jean d', 1918
  - Oultremont, Guy d', 1918
  - Oursler, Grace (Mrs. Fulton), 1953
  - Owen, Herbert, 1918
  - Paderewska, Helena, 1918-1919 (Box 56)
  - Paderewski, Ignacy Jan, 1921-1934
  - The Paderewski Foundation, Inc., N.Y., 1952
  - Page, Arthur W., 1918-1933
  - Page, Frank C., 1923-1931
  - Page, James R., 1927
  - Page, Walter H., 1917
  - Paley, William S., 1930-1932
  - Pallavicino, Ansalde, Count, and Countessa Andreola, 1921-1954
  - Pallavicino, Baby [See: Vinci, Countess]
  - Palmer, Frederick, 1919-1928
  - Pam, Hugo, 1921-1924
  - Parc, Gatien du, Viscount, 1951-1954
  - Parker, Force, 1930-1931
  - Parker, George S., 1929
  - Parraperez, M. C., 1926
  - Parsons, Herbert, 1924
  - Patchin, J. H., 1920
  - Patchin, Philip Halsey, 1918-1932
  - Patchin, Polly (Mrs. Philip), 1954
  - Patchin, Robert H., 1925-1933
  - Pate, 1940
  - Patek, Stanislas, 1920
  - Patterson, Richard, Jr., 1919
  - Paul-Boncour, Joseph, 1930
  - Paulucci, E. Chludzinska, 1921-1930
  - Pavlohhi, M., 1923
  - Pearce, Richard A., 1922
  - Pearson, Alfred J., 1924
  - Peden, Allen N., 1925
  - Peden, E. A., 1926
  - Pell, Robert T., 1932
  - Peltzer, Fernand, 1924-1927
  - Penfield, Walter S., 1924
  - Pennoyer, Richard, 1920-1932
  - Peoples Industrial Trading Corporation, N.Y. [See: O'Laughlin, John Callan]
  - Percy, Eustace, 1924
  - Perlowski, Frank M., 1919
  - Perlowski, Stanislas, 1920
  - Pershing, John J., Gen., 1922
  - Peters, Andrew J., 1927
  - Pfluegh, Harriette, undated
  - Philip, Hoffman, 1920-1932
  - Philippson, M., 1927
  - Phillippe, C. C., undated
  - Phillips, Charles, 1921
  - Phillips, W. E., 1953
  - Phillips, William [See also: SUBJECT FILE, Rogers Bill, Correspondence of Gibson]
    - 1915-1929
    - 1930-1936
  - Picton, Harry, 1922-1923 (Box 57)
  - Piemonte, Maria Jose of, Princess, 1934
  - Pieper, 1927
  - Pierrepont, R. Stuyvesant, 1920-1930
  - Pierrepont, Seth Low, 1920-1921
  - Piltz, Erasme, 1921
  - Pinkham, J. Roy, 1931
  - Piotrowska, Grazyna, 1924
  - Pirenne, Jacques, 1947-1950
  - Pirenne, Jeanne, 1949
  - Podbielski, Rene Gerhard, 1953
  - Poland, William B., 1920-1932
  - Police Federale des Etrangers, Bern, Switzerland (Baechtold, P.), 1954
  - Polish Food Draft Relief (Flint, Motley H.), 1920
  - Politis, Nicolas, 1931
  - Polk, Elisabeth (Mrs. Frank L.), undated
  - Polk, Frank L., 1918-1941
  - Pomona College [See also: Brackett, Frank P.], 1936
  - Poniatowska, Princess, 1923
  - Poole, DeWitt C., 1922-1929
  - Popoff, George, 1926
  - Porras, Belisario, 1926-1927
  - Portales, Marguerite, 1932
  - Porter, Ivy (Mrs. Seton), 1953
  - Porter, Stephen G., 1920-1924
  - Portland, Duc and Duchess of, 1940-1942
  - Potie, undated
  - Potocka
  - Potocka, Anna, Countess, 1922
  - Potocki, Alfred, Count, and Countess Betka, 1919-1953
  - Potocki, George, Count, 1920-1953
  - Potocki, Henry, Count, 1921-1929
  - Potocki, Joseph, Count, 1922-1954
  - Potocki, Roman, 1922
  - Potulicki, Michael, 1953
  - Pousette, Sven Harald, 1919-1929
  - Prendergast, Walter T., 1931
  - Prince, D. C., 1921
  - Prince, John Dynely, 1929-1930
  - Przezdziecki, Etienne, Count, 1921-1922
  - Pulaski, 1919
  - Pulitzer, Joseph, 1928
  - Purcell, J., undated
  - Puslowski, Xavier, Count, 1919-1932
  - Putnam, G. P., 1919-1920
  - Quekemeyer, J. G., 1918
  - Quinn, Cyril J. C. [See also: DIPLOMATIC POSTS, Poland, Relief Work, Correspondence], 1921-1923
  - Quinones de Leon, Jose, 1926-1927
  - Radziszewski, Henry, 1920
  - Radziszewski, J., 1921
  - Radziwill, Felicie [See: Clary, Prince Carlos and Princess Felicie]
  - Raemaekers, Louis, 1929
  - Rand, Elbridge D., 1926-1929
  - Rarogiewicz, E. W., 1921
  - Raulston, Marion Churchill (Mrs. Burrell Otto), undated
  - Ravensdale, Irene, Baroness, 1952
  - Ravndal, G. Bie, 1925-1926
  - Rawlings, H. B., 1921-1922
  - Rawnsley, Claude, 1927
  - The Reader's Digest, Pleasantville, N.Y., 1951-1952
  - Reber, James, 1933
  - Reber, Samuel, 1953
  - Redecker, Sidney Brayton, 1921-1954
  - Reed, David A., 1930
  - Reed, Edward L., 1927-1930
  - Reed, Ralph J., 1929
  - Register, Albert Layton, 1932
  - Regnery, Henry, 1952
  - Regnier, Dr., 1954
  - Reid, John Rogers (Herald Tribune, N.Y.), 1942
  - Reid, Whitelaw, 1910-1911
  - Reinsch, Paul S., 1919
  - Reyntiens, Alice, 1924
  - Reyntiens, Eric, undated
  - Reyntiens, Guy, 1922
  - Reyntiens, Mrs., 1922
  - Rice, Paran F., 1931-1932
  - Richards, Lewis, 1922-1929
  - Richards, Miss, 1926
  - Richardson, Dorsey, 1923-1927
  - Richardson, Gardner, 1921-1952
  - Richardson, Norval, 1918
  - Rickard, Edgar [See also: SUBJECT FILE, C.R.B. Educational Foundation, Inc.] (Box 58)
    - 1918-1921
    - 1922-1925
    - 1926-1929
    - 1930-1939
  - Ridder, A. de, 1931
  - Ringland, Arthur C., 1942
  - Risquez-Iribarren, Rafael, 1954
  - Ristitch, Yovan, 1930
  - Robbins, Warren D. [See also: SUBJECT FILE, Rogers Bill, Correspondence of Gibson]
    - 1920-1923
    - 1924-1933
  - Roberts, Kenneth, 1923-1931 (Box 59)
  - Robins, Robbie, 1954
  - Robinson, Henry M., 1928-1929
  - Robinson, T. Douglas, 1927
  - Rockefeller, David, 1953
  - Roden, Albert Andrews, 1930
  - Rodman, Willoughby and Arabella, 1920-1921
  - Rogers, Edith Louise, 1925
  - Rogers, James Grafton, 1933-1941
  - Rogers, Leighton W. [See also: SUBJECT FILE, Rogers Bill, Correspondence of Gibson], 1923-1924
  - Rogers, Louise de G., 1919-1920
  - Rogers, Walter S., 1920
  - Romeike, Henry, Inc., N.Y., 1919-1930
  - Romer, E., 1921
  - Roosevelt, Eleanor (Mrs. Theodore), 1941-1954
  - Roosevelt, Frances (Mrs. Quentin), 1953
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano, 1920-1942
  - Roosevelt, Theodore, 1938-1944
  - Rossi Longhi, Alberto, 1953-1954
  - Rossi Longhi, Fabrizio, 1954
  - Rossi Longhi, Roberto, 1953
  - Rosso, A., 1930-1932
  - Rousseau, Theodore, 1919-1931
  - Rowe, Leo S., 1924-1933
  - Roy, Lieut. du, 1922
  - Roy, A. C., 1923
  - Roy de Blicquy, Minime (Mrs. Jean du), 1954
  - Rozycki, Ludomir, 1921
  - Ruddock, Albert B., 1919-1927
  - Ruhl(?), Arthur, 1920
  - Rumbold, Horace, Sir, and Lady, 1921-1928
  - Rumrill, L. L., 1951
  - Runyon, Ralph C., 1929
  - Ryan, Edward, undated
  - Ryan, Ethel M., 1953-1954
  - Ryan, T. R., Maj., 1920-1921
  - Ryott, Harold A., 1919-1922
  - Rzewnski, 1926
  - Rzyszczewska, Emily, Countess, 1921
  - Sackett, Frederic M., 1932
  - Sage, Robert, undated
  - Salmon, David A., 1927
  - Salvation Army, Brussels [See: Armee du Salut]
  - Sands, William Franklin, 1919-1930
  - Saphro, Elisabeth MacVeen, 1926
  - Sapieha, Leon, Prince, 1928
  - Sapieha, Theresa, Princess, 1954
  - Sartiges, Count de, 1927
  - Sartori di Montecroce, Anna, Baroness, 1933
  - Sartorius, Herman U., (?), 1920-1934
  - Sato, M. N., 1929
  - Satterlee, Herbert L., 1926
  - Savage, Catherine Comer (Mrs. Robert), 1954
  - Savery, Frank, 1921-1924
  - Savinkoff(?), B., 1920
  - Sawicki, Joseph F., 1920-1938
  - Schell, Frank R., 1920
  - Schelling, Ernest, 1922-1933
  - Schmettau, Charles A., 1928
  - Schmid, C., 1925
  - Schmidt, Josef, 1932
  - Schnessler, William C., 1927
  - Schoeffter, Martin George, undated
  - Schoenfeld, H. F. Arthur, 1923
  - Schofield, Frank H., Adm., 1927-1928
  - Schurman, Jacob Gould, 1927
  - Schwartz, Abba, 1953
  - Schwarzenberg, Jean, Princess, 1952-1953
  - Schwenker, W. M., 1920
  - Scidmore, Eliza R., 1928
  - Scoggin, H. D., 1930-1931
  - Scott, James Brown, undated
  - Scott, Mabel Janet, 1925
  - Search, Preston W., 1927
  - Searchinger, Cesar, 1930
  - Seaver, Frank R., 1927
  - Sebastian, Sr. M., 1952
  - See, Fong F., 1922
  - Seidner, Emeric, 1930
  - Sengier, E., 1924
  - Serre-Sanlaville, E., 1932
  - Shaler, Millard King [See also: SUBJECT FILE, C.R.B. Educational Foundation, Inc.] (Box 60)
    - 1915
    - 1920-1929
    - 1930-1933
  - Sharkey, Joseph E., 1927-1931
  - Sharp, Mrs., 1929
  - Shaw, G. Howland [See also: SUBJECT FILE, Rogers Bill, Correspondence of Gibson], 1926
  - Sheffield, James Rockwell, 1926
  - Shepardson, Whitney, 1919-1921
  - Sheppard, Morris, 1926
  - Sheppey, Marshall, 1926
  - Sherman, H. G., 1931
  - Sherrill, C. H., Gen., 1927-1932
  - Sherwood, Renaud, 1926
  - Shipley, Ruth B., 1952
  - Shirrill, Charles H., 1927
  - Shoecraft, Eugene C., 1919-1932
  - Sholes, 1933
  - Shotwell, James T., 1930
  - Shuster, George N., 1952
  - Shutter, Joseph, 1932
  - Sikorski, Gen., 1928
  - Silvercruys, Franz, 1928-1933
  - Simon, John, Sir, 1932
  - Simpson, John Lowrey, 1921
  - Simonds, George S., Gen., 1927-1932
  - Simonson, Warren and Maude, 1952-1954
  - Sincay, Gaston, 1924
  - Singer, W. H., Jr., 1932
  - Skrzynski, Alexandre, Count, 1920
  - Smiddy, T. C., 1930
  - Smith, Alice Rapalge, 1929
  - Smith, Aubrey, Sir, Adm., 1924-1954
  - Smith, Carroll L., 1927
  - Smith, Dorothy M. and Larry, (?), 1952-1954
  - Smith, Edgar W., 1924
  - Smith, H. Alexander, 1924-1953
  - Smith, Helen D. (Mrs. H. Alexander), undated
  - Smith, Henry B., 1922-1928
  - Smith, Marc, 1929-1933
  - Smith, Mildred Witchell (Mrs. Beardslee), 1924-1930
  - Smith, Paul C., 1953-1954
  - Smith, Sarah B. (Mrs. Paul Jordan), 1929
  - Smith, Thomas, 1927
  - Smith, William Walker, 1924-1928
  - Smulski, John F., 1920-1922
  - Smuts, Jan Christian, 1943
  - Smyth, W. W., Capt., 1927-1933
  - Snively, John R., 1927
  - Sobanska, Marie, Countess, 1922-1931
  - Sobanski, Ladislas, 1921-1922
  - Sokal, F., 1927
  - Sokolowski, Venceslas de, 1921
  - Solvay, Louis, 1927-1950s
  - Souchon, Lucien, 1932
  - Southerland, Katherine, 1924-1925
  - Southwest Museum, Los Angeles, 1952
  - Spalding, William D., 1924-1930
  - Spanish Embassy, Paris, 1926
  - Spencer, Willing, 1920
  - Spender, Hugh F., 1926-1927
  - Sperling, Rowland, 1924-1930
  - Sperry, William H., 1921
  - Speyer, H., 1931
  - Spoelberch, Eric de, 1926-1933
  - Spoelberch, Guillaume de, Viscount, 1927-1929
  - The Spur, N.Y. (Tobin, Agnes E.), 1927
  - Squiers, Arnon L., 1921 (Box 61)
  - St. Phalle, Francois de, 1920-1923
  - Stabler, Jordan Herbert, 1920-1930
  - Stahl, Carl A., 1923
  - Stalinski, Jan, 1933
  - Starret, Henry P., 1920-1931
  - Stearns, Frank W., 1924-1932
  - Steenhault, Baron, 1925-1929
  - Stephen, Robert Frost, Mrs. See King, Alice
  - Stephens, D. S., Mrs., 1928-1930
  - Sterling, Frederick A., 1919-1954
  - Stetson, Clarence C., 1920-1926
  - Stetson, John B., Jr., 1925
  - Stettinius, Edward Reily, 1919
  - Stevens, Laurence Sterne, 1925
  - Stewart, John K., 1952-1953
  - Stewart, Mary, undated
  - Stewart, Nathaniel B., 1929
  - Stimson, Henry L., 1929-1933
  - Stockton, Gilchrist B.
    - 1918-1929
    - 1930-1933
  - Stoermer, Grace S. (National Statuary Hall, Washington, D.C.), 1933
  - Stoever, Edward R., 1923
  - Stone, Donald, 1918
  - Stone(?), Tommy, 1954
  - Stone, William T., 1931
  - Storey, Charles M., 1922
  - Stotesbury, Edward T., 1923
  - Stovall, Pleasant A., 1920
  - Stowell, Ellery C. [See also: Garner, Wilford J. and SUBJECT FILE, Rogers Bill, Correspondence of Gibson], 1927-1933
  - Straten, Robert van der, Count, 1933-1935
  - Straten Ponthoz, Roger van der, Count, 1953-1954
  - Strauss, Lewis L., 1918-1952
  - Streit, C. K., 1931
  - Strong, George V., 1927-1932
  - Strother, French, 1928-1930
  - Stull, William, 1921
  - Sturges, Jeanne (Mrs. Hollister), undated
  - Sullivan, Mark, 1930-1931
  - Summerlin, George Thomas, 1920-1931
  - Super, Paul, 1923
  - Sussex County Magazine, Eastbourne, Great Britain, 1930
  - Sutherland, Jane, 1928-1932
  - Sutliff, Milo J., 1951
  - Suydam, Henry, 1921
  - Swaelus-Godenne, L. [See also: Shaler, Millard King], 1928-1932
  - Swanson, Claude A., 1932-1933
  - Sweetser, Arthur, 1920-1932
  - Swett, Trevor, 1932-1933 (Box 62)
  - Swift, Merrit Wesley, 1923-1930
  - Symington, Pete, Capt., 1926
  - Szapary, Eilzabeth, Countess, 1954
  - Szczeniawski, I., 1919-1922
  - Szechenyi, Laszlo, 1932
  - Taft, Robert A., 1919-1943
  - Talbot, Clare Ryan (Mrs. E. C.), 1934
  - Tanco e Argaez, Mrs., undated
  - Tarler, G. Cornell, 1920
  - Taylor, Alonzo E., 1921-1936
  - Taylor, Henry J., 1943
  - Taylor, Josephine, 1924
  - Taylor, R. M., 1922
  - Taylor, William H., 1926
  - Terry, Prentiss M., 1927
  - Thakara, A. M., 1933
  - Thaw, Benjamin T., Jr., 1920-1932
  - Thayer, P. M. (Mrs. Nathaniel), undated
  - Theodoli, Ugo, 1953-1954
  - Theunis, George [See: Aubert, Theodore]
  - Thomas, Albert, 1925-1926
  - Thomas, Frances R. (Mrs. Lowell), 1953
  - Thomas, John R., Jr., 1930-1931
  - Thomas, Julian M., 1930
  - Thomas, Lowell, 1943-1954
  - Thomas, Norman, 1942
  - Thompson, Llewellyn E., Jr., 1953
  - Thompson, W., 1927-1933
  - Thomson, Basil, 1926
  - Thomson, Lord, 1930
  - Thornburg, Pherbia, Jr., 1953-1954
  - Thornburg, Raymond and Pherbia, 1952-1954
  - Thurston, Walter C., 1933-1934
  - Thys, R.(?), 1931
  - Times Book Club, London, 1927-1933
  - Titcomb, George E., Mrs., 1927
  - Tittman, Harold, 1931
  - Titulesco, 1932
  - Titus, Paul, 1933-1934
  - Tobin, Richard M., 1929-1933
  - Topping, Thomas T., 1924-1931
  - Torrey, Clare, 1922-1928
  - Totten, Ralph J., 1929-1930
  - Tovvem(?), Marquis of, 1926
  - Townsend, Laurence, Mrs., undated
  - Trafford, Betty, 1931-1936
  - Train, Harold C., 1927-1931
  - Trainor, Joseph H., 1920-1929
  - Trapp, Robert, 1922
  - Traus, Edouard, 1927-1931
  - Traux, Bon de, 1927
  - Travess, Howard, 1954
  - Treanor, John, 1928
  - Trippe, Juan T., 1934
  - Trippet, Cora W. L. (Mrs. Oscar A.), 1932
  - Trissel, Sam B., 1927
  - Tronchin, Mr., 1932
  - Tronor, Edward, 1926
  - Tropin, Ruth, undated
  - Tucholka, L., 1921
  - Tuck, Alec J. M., 1953
  - Tuck, S. Pinckney [See also: Cheney, Charles H.], 1924-1954
  - Tuck, William Hallam [See also: SUBJECT FILE, C.R.B. Educational Foundation, Inc.] (Box 63)
    - 1920-1929
    - 1930-1954
  - Tucker, Albert J., Maj., 1926
  - Tucker, H. C., Rev., 1933
  - Tuckerman, Walter, 1921
  - Turner, Campbell, 1934-1935
  - Turner, Norman, Capt., 1925
  - TWA Ambassadors Club, N.Y., 1954
  - Twitchell, Kenaston, 1932
  - Tyler, Royall, 1952
  - Tyng, S. T., 1919
  - Tyszkiewicz, Rose (Countess Benoit), 1929
  - Ullens de Schooten, Jean and Marie-Therese, 1932-1954
  - United Press Associations, N.Y., 1930
  - United States. Department of State, 1920
  - United States. Department of the Treasury, 1941
  - University Club of Los Angeles (Thompson, Oscar), 1924-1925
  - University of Brussels, 1930
  - Urquhart, Augusta W., 1929
  - Ursel, Louis d', Count, undated
  - Vacuum Oil Company, N.Y., 1924
  - Valuyeff, Serge and Macha, 1924-1954
  - Van Coover, Jeanne, 1932
  - Van Dyke, Henry, 1915-1921
  - Van Dyke, Paul, 1921
  - Van Heuven, Goedhart, 1954
  - Van Horne, E. J., 1953-1954
  - Van Keuren, A. H., 1932
  - Van Maldeghem, Pierre, 1931
  - Van Norman, Louis E., 1921-1934
  - Van Rensselaer, W. S., 1929
  - Van Snick-Koslowski, Alph., 1929-1930
  - Van Truen, C. P., 1931
  - Vanderhoof, Ruth (Mrs. Ralph Scovell), 1932-1953
  - Vandoren, Josy, 1927
  - Vane, Francis Fletcher, 1929
  - Vansittart, Robert, 1931
  - Vauclain, Samuel, 1920-1933
  - Vaufrelant, Georges de, Baron, 1932
  - Vaufrelant, Louis de, Baron, undated
  - Vaughan, George, 1925
  - Veilborg, Kay, 1933
  - Vigano, Beatrice, 1929
  - Villalobar, Rodrigo and Marquise de, Marquis, 1915-1929
  - Villaret, 1926
  - Villenfagne, Baron de, 1932
  - Vinci, Baby, Countess (born Pallavicino), 1922-1933
  - Virden, Ray, undated
  - Visson, Andre, Mrs., 1953
  - Vollen, 1924
  - Vos, J. M., 1952-1954
  - Vulliamy, A. C., 1922
  - Wadsworth, Craig W., 1922-1930's
  - Wadsworth, Eliot, 1920-1936
  - Wadsworth, James W., 1926
  - Wagoner, Clarence R., 1927
  - Waha, Raymond de, Baron, 1932